

# Emir Mertoğlu

Full-Stack Developer

📞 +905303001197 🔀 emir.mertoglu.97@gmail.com 🛚 in emirmertoglu

🔘 emirxmertoglu 💆 emirxmertoglu 🤘 emirxmertoglu.github.io

## **■ Profile**

I have hands-on experience efficiently coding websites and applications using modern HTML, CSS, JavaScript and .NET.

Building state-of-the-art, easy-to-use, user-friendly websites and applications is truly a passion of mine and I am confident I would be an excellent addition to the organization that I work for. In addition to my knowledge base, I actively seek out new technologies and stay up-to-date on industry trends and advancements.

# Skills

React

Vue.Js

Node.Js

JavaScript

JSON

• HTML5

CSS3

.NET

ASP.NET

Flutter

C#

• (

Python

Firebase

• Git

# Professional Experience

#### Gelecek Varlık FullStack Bootcamp Student,

11/2021 - 01/2022

Patika.dev 2

We learned .NET Core and React

#### Front-End Developer Intern, Nutima Code ☑

03/2021 - 10/2021



#### V-Book 🗷

A web app where you can view the top 100 classical books. I use Vue.Js & Vue Router & Json-Server with this project

### COVID-19 Turkey Data ☑

My goal in this project is to analyze the coronavirus data in the data set to make it meaningful and visualize it.

Kaggle link ☑

**Stuvent Mobile,** for IEEEmadC | Mobile Application Development Contest My goal in this project is to announce the events that will take place at the university through the mobile application.

# **Organisations**

### GDG Mugla, Organizer and Developer ☑

09/2020 - 03/2021

When you join a Google Developer Group, you'll have the opportunity to meet local developers with similar interests in technology. A GDG meetup event includes talks on a wide range of technical topics where you can learn new skills through hands-on workshops. The community prides itself on being an inclusive environment where everyone and anyone interested in tech - from beginner developers to experienced professionals - all are welcome to join.

- I organized and helped with some events.
- I developed the GDG&WTM Mugla website.

### **DSC MSKU,** Core Team Member 🗷

08/2019 - 08/2020

Developer Student Clubs are university-based community groups for students interested in Google developer technologies. By joining a DSC, students grow their knowledge in a peer-to-peer learning environment and build solutions for local businesses and their community.

• I organized and helped with some events.



### Languages

**English**Professional working competence
Native

## **Education**

**Information Systems Engineering,** 09/2018 – 06/2022

Mugla Sitki Kocman University

GPA: +3.5/4

**Management of Health Institutions,** 09/2015 – 06/2018

Anadolu University

**Paramedic, Nisantasi University** 09/2015 – 06/2017



### **Computer Aided Advertising and Design**

I can use most of Adobe Technologies: Photoshop, Illustrator, InDesign, etc.

# Cisco Networking Academy Mobility Fundamentals course, and demonstrating the ability to do following:

Wireless technologies, Wireless LAN standarts, Wireless LAN access point, router and client, Wireless LAN security, troubleshoot Wireless LANs

# Cisco Networking Academy Introduction to Cybersecurity course, and demonstrating the ability to explain the following:

Global implications of cyber threats, Ways in which networks are vulnerable to attack, Impact of cyber-attacks on industries, Cisco's approach to threats detection and defense